CONTÉM IMAGENS
QUE PODEM AFETAR EPILÉTICOS
E OUTRAS PESSOAS FOTOSSENSÍVEIS.
TENHA PRUDÊNCIA AO ASSISTIR.
It's been a long time
Coming
It's been a long time coming
It's been a long time...
It's you and me...
It's been a long time coming
It's fearless
Big reputation
It's been
a long time coming. but
And they said. "Speak now"
It's been a long time coming
Into folklore
Meu nome é Taylor e nasci em 1989.
It's been a long time coming
Loving him was red
Re-e-e-ed. re-e-e-ed
Meet me at midnight
Lover
Nice
It's been
a long time coming. but
It's you and me
That's my whole world
They whisper in the hallway
"She's a bad. bad girl"
Okay
The whole school
is rolling fake dice
You play stupid games
You win stupid prizes
It's you and me
There's nothing like this
Miss Americana
and The Heartbreak Prince
Okay
We're so sad
We paint the town blue
Voted most likely
to run away
Most likely to run away
Voted most likely
to run away
With you
Oi!
Fever dream high
in the quiet of the night
You know that I caught it
Bad. bad boy
Shiny toy with a price
You know that I bought it
Killing me slow
Out the window
I'm always waiting for you
to be waiting below
Devils roll the dice
Angels roll their eyes
What doesn't kill me
makes me want you more
And it's new
The shape of your body
It's blue
The feeling I've got
And it's ooh. whoa.
It's a cruel summer
It's cool
That's what I tell 'em
No rules in breakable heaven
But ooh. whoa.
It's a cruel summer
With you
Hang your head low
In the glow
of the vending machine
I'm not dying
You say
that we'll just screw it up
In these trying times
We're not trying
So cut the headlights
Summer's a knife
I'm always waiting for you
just to cut to the bone
Devils roll the dice
Angels roll their eyes
And if I bleed
You'll be the last to know
It's new
The shape of your body
It's blue
The feeling I've got
And it's ooh. whoa.
It's a cruel summer
It's cool
That's what I tell 'em
No rules in breakable heaven
But ooh. whoa.
It's a cruel summer
With you
Certo. Los Angeles.
chegamos na primeira ponte da noite.
Tenho uma pergunta.
Alguém aqui sabe a letra dessa ponte?
Provem!
I'm drunk
in the back of the car
And I cried like a baby
coming home from the bar
Said. "I'm fine"
But it wasn't true
I don't wanna keep secrets
just to keep you
And I snuck in
through the garden gate
Every night that summer
just to seal my fate
And I screamed
for whatever it's worth
"I love you"
Ain't that the worst thing
you ever heard?
He looks up
grinning like a devil
It's new
The shape of your body
It's blue
The feeling I've got
And it's ooh. whoa.
It's a cruel summer
It's cool
That's what I tell 'em
No rules in breakable heaven
- But
- Ooh. whoa.
It's a cruel summer
I'm drunk
in the back of the car
And I cried like a baby
coming home from the bar
Said. "I'm fine"
But it wasn't true
I don't wanna keep secrets
just to keep you
And I snuck in
through the garden gate
Every night that summer
just to seal my fate
And I screamed
for whatever it's worth
"I love you"
Ain't that the worst thing
you ever heard?
Cruel summer with you
With you
With you. with you
It's a cruel summer
With you
With you. with you
It's a cruel summer
Ai. Los Angeles.
estão me fazendo me sentir fantástica.
Pensando bem.
vou experimentar uma coisa.
Quer dizer...
está ficando perigoso.
Está subindo
à minha cabeça bem rápido.
Vocês me fazem sentir tão...
tão poderosa.
Sim.
Vocês me fazem sentir...
como se eu pudesse fazer
um show esgotado no Estádio SoFi hoje.
Vocês me fazem sentir
como se eu fosse "The Man".
I would be complex
I would be cool
They'd say
I played the field
Before I found
someone to commit to
And that would be okay
For me to do
Every conquest I had made
Would make me
more of a boss to you
I'd be a fearless leader
I'd be an alpha type
When everyone believes ya
What's that like?
I'm so sick of running
as fast as I can
Wondering if I'd get there quicker
If I was a man
And I'm so sick of them
coming at me again
'Cause if I was a man
Then I'd be the man
- I'd be the man
- Man
They'd say I hustled
Put in the work
They wouldn't
shake their heads
And question
how much of this I deserve
What I was wearing
If I was rude
Could all be separated
From my good ideas
and power moves
And they would
toast to me.
- Hey!
- Let the players play
I'd be just like Leo
In Saint-Tropez
I'm so sick of running
as fast as I can
Wondering if I'd get there quicker
If I was a man
And I'm so sick of them
coming at me again
'Cause if I was a man
Then I'd be the man
- I'd be the man
- Man
What's it like
to brag about
Raking in dollars
And getting
bitches and models
And it's all good
if you're bad
And it's okay
if you're mad
If I was out
flashing my dollars
I'd be a bitch. not a baller
They'd paint me out
to be bad
So it's okay that I'm mad
I'm so sick of running
as fast as I can
Wondering if I'd get there quicker
If I was a man
And I'm so sick of them
coming at me again
'Cause if I was a man
- Then I'd be the man
- BACKUP SINGERS: Hey!
I'm so sick of running
as fast as I can
Wondering if I'd get there quicker
If I was a man
And I'm so sick of them
coming at me again
'Cause if I was a man
Then I'd be the man
- I'd be the man
- BACKUP SINGERS: Man
- Man
- I'd be the man
- BACKUP SINGERS: Man
If I was a man
Then I'd be the man
You are somebody
that we don't know
But you're coming
at my friends like a missile
Why are you mad?
When you could be GLAAD?
GLAAD
Sunshine on the street
at the parade
But you would rather be
in the dark ages
Making that sign
Must've taken all night
You just need
to take several seats
And then try
to restore the peace
And control your urges
to scream
About all the people
you hate
'Cause shade never made
anybody less gay so
So.
You need to calm down
You're being too loud
And I'm just like
You need to just stop
Like. can you just
not step on his gown?
You need to calm down
And we see you over there
on the Internet
Comparing all the girls
who are killing it
But we figured you out
We all know now
We all got crowns
You need to calm down
Quero ver suas mãos!
You're being too loud
And I'm just like
You need to just stop
Can you stop?
Like. can you just
not step on our gowns?
You need to calm down
É uma honra e um prazer
dizer estas palavras para vocês.
Bem-vindos ao The Eras Tour.
Olha só para vocês.
Olha só com quem vou cantar hoje.
Vou cantar e dançar com vocês.
vibrar com vocês
e passar a noite com vocês.
Temos uma boa noção da plateia
nas primeiras músicas.
Sabemos se será uma situação
de almas gêmeas com a plateia.
e sinto que é promissor.
Só tenho que dizer isso. Está bonito.
Vocês e eu estamos prestes a partir
em uma pequena aventura juntos.
E essa aventura vai durar
17 anos de música.
uma era de cada vez.
O que acham?
Vou contar meu sonho secreto
para esta noite.
Essas são músicas
que compus sobre minha vida
ou sentimentos em dado momento.
seja na adolescência.
na casa dos 20 anos ou uns anos atrás.
mas depois de hoje.
quando ouvirem essas músicas por aí.
meu sonho é
que vocês pensem sobre esta noite
e as memórias
que criamos juntos no Estádio SoFi.
Serei sua anfitriã hoje.
Meu nome é Taylor.
Obrigada por viajar conosco
aqui no The Eras Tour.
We could leave the
Christmas lights up till January
This is our place
We make the rules
And there's a dazzling haze
A mysterious way
about you. dear
Have I known you
20 seconds or 20 years?
Can I go where you go?
Can we always be this close?
Forever and ever. and.
Take me out
and take me home
You're my. my. my. my
Lover
We could let our friends
crash in the living room
This is our place
We make the call
And I'm highly suspicious
That everyone who sees you
wants you
I've loved you
three summers now. honey
But I want 'em all
Can I go where you go?
Can we always be this close?
Forever and ever. and.
Take me out
and take me home
Forever and ever
You're my. my. my. my
Lover
Ladies and gentlemen
Will you please stand?
With every guitar string
scar on my hand
I take this magnetic force
of a man to be my lover
My heart's been borrowed
and yours has been blue
All's well that ends well
to end up with you
Swear to be overdramatic
and true to my lover
And you'll save
All your dirtiest jokes for me
And at every table
I'll save you a seat
Lover
Can I go where you go?
Can we always be this close?
Forever and ever. and.
Take me out
and take me home
Forever and ever
You're my. my. my. my
Darling
Lover
There's something
about the way
The street looks
when it's just rained
There's a glow
off the pavement
You walk me to the car
And you know I wanna
ask you to dance right there
In the middle
of the parking lot
Yeah
We're drivin' down the road
I wonder if you know
I'm trying so hard
not to get caught up now
But you're just so cool
Run your hands
through your hair
Absentmindedly makin' me want you
And I don't know
how it gets better than this
You take my hand and drag me
headfirst. fearless
And I don't know why
but with you I'd dance
In a storm in my best dress Fearless
Well. you stood there
with me in the doorway
My hands shake
I'm not usually this way
But you pull me in
and I'm a little more brave
It's the first kiss
it's flawless
Really somethin'
It's fearless
Yeah
And I don't know
how it gets better than this
You take my hand and drag me
headfirst. fearless
And I don't know why
but with you I'd dance
In a storm in my best dress Fearless
Yeah
All right. L.A..
are you ready
to go back
to high school with me?
You're on the phone
with your girlfriend
She's upset
She's going off about
something that you said
She doesn't
get your humor like I do
I'm in my room
It's a typical Tuesday night
I'm listening to the kind
of music she doesn't like
And she'll never
know your story like I do
But she wears short skirts
I wear T-shirts
She's cheer captain
and I'm on the bleachers
Dreaming about the day
when you wake up and find
That what you're looking for
has been here the whole time
If you could see
that I'm the one
Who understands you
Been here all along
So. why can't you see?
You belong with me
Walk in the streets with you
in your worn-out jeans
I can't help thinking
this is how it ought to be
Laughing on a park bench
thinking to myself
Hey. isn't this easy?
And you've got a smile
That can light up
this whole town
I haven't seen it in a while
since she brought you down
You say you're fine
I know you better than that
Hey. what you doing
with a girl like that?
She wears high heels
I wear sneakers
She's cheer captain
and I'm on the bleachers
Dreaming about the day
when you wake up and find
That what you're looking for
has been here the whole time
If you could see
that I'm the one
Who understands you
Been here all along
So. why can't you see?
You belong with me
Standing by
and waiting at your back door
All this time
How could
you not know. baby?
You belong with me
I remember you
driving to my house
In the middle of the night
I'm the one
who makes you laugh
When you know
you're 'bout to cry
I know your favorite songs
And you tell me
'bout your dreams
Think I know
where you belong
Think I know it's with me
Can't you see
that I'm the one
Who understands you?
Been here all along
So. why can't you see?
You belong with me
Standing by
and waiting at your back door
All this time
How could
you not know. baby?
You belong with me
Have you ever thought
just maybe
You belong with me
We were both young
when I first saw you
I close my eyes
and the flashback starts
I'm standin' there
On a balcony in summer air
See the lights
See the party
The ball gowns
See you make your way
through the crowd
And say. "Hello"
Little did I know
That you were Romeo
You were throwin' pebbles
And my daddy said
"Stay away from Juliet"
And I was cryin'
on the staircase
Beggin' you
"Please don't go"
And I said
Romeo. take me
somewhere we can be alone
I'll be waiting
All there's left to do
is run
You'll be the prince
and I'll be the princess
It's a love story
Baby. just say. "Yes"
So I sneak out
to the garden to see you
We keep quiet
'Cause we're dead
if they knew
So close your eyes
Escape this town
for a little while.
'Cause you were Romeo
I was a scarlet letter
And my daddy said
"Stay away from Juliet"
But you were everything
to me
I was beggin' you
"Please don't go"
And I said
Romeo. take me
somewhere we can be alone
I'll be waiting
All there's left to do
is run
You'll be the prince
and I'll be the princess
It's a love story
Baby. just say. "Yes"
Romeo. save me
They're tryna tell me
how to feel
This love is difficult
But it's real
Don't be afraid
We'll make it
out of this mess
It's a love story
Baby. just say. "Yes"
I got tired of waiting
Wonderin' if you were
ever comin' around
My faith in you was fading
When I met you
on the outskirts of town
And I said
Romeo. save me
I've been feeling so alone
I keep waiting for you
but you never come
Is this in my head?
I don't know what to think
He knelt to the ground
And pulled out a ring
And said
"Marry me. Juliet
"You'll never
have to be alone
"I love you
and that's all I really know
"I talked to your dad
Go pick out a white dress
"It's a love story
Baby. just say. 'Yes'"
'Cause we were both young
when I first saw you
Wait for the signal
And I'll meet you
after dark
I'm like the water
When your ship
rolled in that night
Rough on the surface
But you cut through
like a knife
And if it was
an open-shut case
I never would've known
from the look on your face
Lost in your current
like a priceless wine
The more that you say
The less I know
Wherever you stray
I follow
I'm begging for you
to take my hand
Wreck my plans
That's my man
Life was a willow
And it bent
right to your wind
Head on the pillow
I could feel you sneaking in
As if you were
a mythical thing
Like you were a trophy
or a champion ring
And there was one prize
I'd cheat to win
The more that you say
The less I know
Wherever you stray
I follow
I'm begging for you
to take my hand
Wreck my plans
That's my man
You know that my train
could take you home
Anywhere else is hollow
I'm begging for you
to take my hand
Wreck my plans
That's my man
Life was a willow
And it bent
right to your wind
They count me out
time and time again
Life was a willow
And it bent
right to your wind
But I come back stronger
than a '90s trend
Wait for the signal
And I'll meet you
after dark
Show me the places where
the others gave you scars
Now this is
an open-shut case
Guess I should've known
from the look on your face
Every bait and switch
was a work of art
The more that you say
The less I know
Wherever you stray
I follow
Begging for you
to take my hand
Wreck my plans
That's my man
You know that my train
could take you home
Anywhere else is hollow
Begging for you
to take my hand
Wreck my plans
That's my man
The more that you say
The less I know
Wherever you stray
I follow
Begging for you
to take my hand
Wreck my plans
That's my man
You know that my train
could take you home
Anywhere else is hollow
Begging for you
to take my hand
Wreck my plans
That's my man
Hey. that's my man
Yeah. that's my man
Every bait and switch
was a work of art
That's my man
Hey. that's my man
I'm begging for you
to take my hand
Wreck my plans
That's my man
Never be so kind
You forget to be clever
Never be so clever
You forget to be kind
And if I didn't know better
I'd think you were
talking to me now
If I didn't know better
I'd think
you were still around
What died didn't stay dead
You're alive
You're alive in my head
What died didn't stay dead
You're alive. so alive
The autumn chill
that wakes me up
You loved the amber skies
so much
Long limbs
and frozen swims
You'd always go past
where our feet could touch
And I complained
the whole way there
The car ride back
and up the stairs
I should've
asked you questions
asked you how to be
Asked you
to write it down for me
Should've kept
every grocery store receipt
'Cause every scrap of you
would be taken from me
Watched as you signed
your name Marjorie
All your closets
of backlogged dreams
And how you left them all
to me
What died didn't stay dead
You're alive
You're alive in my head
What died didn't stay dead
You're alive. so alive
And if I didn't
know better
I'd think you were
singing to me now
If I didn't know better
I'd think
you were still around
I know better
But I still feel you
all around
I know better
But you're still around
Sabem. esta turnê.
o fato de que esta é a última cidade
na turnê pelos EUA.
É tanta coisa para mim.
porque esta foi
a experiência mais extraordinária
de toda a minha vida.
Estar nesta turnê. poder compartilhar
esses momentos com vocês.
Eu sei que eu devia ser blasé.
"Gosto um pouco de vocês."
Mas. de verdade. significou mais
pra mim do que tudo que eu já fiz
ou fez parte da minha vida.
Esta turnê. Então...
Antes da turnê.
eu passava pelo processo
de gravar um álbum.
e eu chamava o álbum de algo
como "Red". "Speak Now" ou "Fearless".
Aí. eu organizava a turnê
com o nome daquele álbum. certo?
Como a turnê 1989. a turnê Speak Now.
Era assim que a gente fazia.
E eu me lembro. por que estou só...
O que é isso?
Por quê?
De qualquer forma. esta turnê...
As pessoas me diziam:
"Você lançou cinco álbuns
para os quais você não fez turnês.
Qual é o seu plano? O que vai fazer?
Você vai fazer um show
com todos os álbuns
e terá umas três horas e meia?"
E eu dizia: "Sim. vai ser chamado
de The Eras Tour. Vejo você lá."
Então estamos agora
na Era Evermore e...
esse foi meu segundo álbum pandêmico.
E havia uma música específica
que compus e depois pensei
que seria uma experiência catártica
cantar "Champagne Problems"
em um estádio. entendem?
Então. vamos lá.
You booked the night train
for a reason
So you could sit there
in this hurt
Bustling crowds
or silent sleepers
You're not sure
which is worse
Because I dropped your hand
while dancing
Left you out there standing
Crestfallen on the landing
Champagne problems
Your mom's ring
in your pocket
My picture in your wallet
Your heart was glass
I dropped it
Champagne problems
You told your family
for a reason
You couldn't keep it in
Your sister splashed out
on the bottle
Now no one's celebrating
Dom Pérignon. you brought it
No crowd of friends applauded
Your hometown skeptics
called it
Champagne problems
You had a speech
You're speechless
Love slipped
beyond your reaches
And I couldn't
give a reason
Champagne problems
Your Midas touch
on the Chevy door
November flush
and your flannel cure
"This dorm was
once a madhouse"
I made a joke
"Well. it's made for me"
How evergreen
Our group of friends
Don't think
we'll say that word again
And soon they'll have
the nerve to deck the halls
That we once walked through
One for the money
Two for the show
I never was ready
so I watch you go
Sometimes you just
don't know the answer
Till someone's
on their knees and asks you
"She would've made
such a lovely bride
"What a shame she's fucked
in the head." they said
But you'll find
the real thing instead
She'll patch up
your tapestry that I shred
And hold your hand
while dancing
Never leave you standing
Crestfallen on the landing
With champagne problems
Your mom's ring
in your pocket
Her picture in your wallet
You won't remember all my
Champagne problems
Pra mim?
É uma coisa muito generosa
de fazer pra uma pessoa. Obrigada.
Thank you so much.
I sit and watch you
reading with your head low
I wake and watch you
Breathing with your eyes closed
I sit and watch you
I notice everything
you do or don't do
You're so much older
and wiser and I
I wait by the door
like I'm just a kid
Use my best colors
for your portrait
Lay the table
with the fancy shit
And watch you tolerate it
If it's all in my head
Tell me now
Tell me
I've got it wrong somehow
I know my love
should be celebrated
But you tolerate it
While you were out building
other worlds. where was I?
Where's that man
Who'd throw blankets
over my barbed wire?
I made you my temple
My mural. my sky
Now I'm begging
for footnotes
In the story of your life
Drawing hearts
in the byline
Always taking up
too much space or time
You assume I'm fine
But what would you do if I
Break free
and leave us in ruins
Took this dagger in me
and removed it
Gain the weight of you
Then lose it
Believe me. I could do it
If it's all in my head
Tell me now
Tell me
I've got it wrong somehow
I know my love
should be celebrated
But you tolerate it
I sit and watch you
Knew he was a killer
first time that I saw him
Wondered how many girls
He had loved
and left haunted
But if he's a ghost
Then I can be a phantom
Holdin' him
for ransom. some
Some boys
are tryin' too hard
He don't try at all though
Younger than my exes
But he act
like such a man. so
I see nothing better
I keep him forever
Like a vendetta-ta
I. I. I see
how this is gon' go
Touch me
and you'll never be alone
I-Island breeze
and lights down low
No one has to know
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
You should see
the things we do. baby
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
I know I'm gonna be
with you. so I take my time
Are you ready for it?
Knew I was a robber
first time that he saw me
Stealing hearts
and running off
And never sayin' sorry
But if I'm a thief
Then he can
join the heist. and
We'll move
to an island. and
And he can be my jailer
Burton to this Taylor
Every love I've known
in comparison is a failure
I forget their names now
I'm so very tame now
Never be the same now. now
I. I. I see
how this is gon' go
Touch me
and you'll never be alone
I-Island breeze
and lights down low
- No one has to know
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
You should see
the things we do. baby
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
I know I'm gonna be
with you. so I take my time
Are you ready for it?
Baby. let the games begin
Let the games begin
I. I. I see
how this is gon' go
Touch me
and you'll never be alone
I-Island breeze
and lights down low
No one has to know
In the middle of the night
Yeah
- In my dreams
- My dreams
You should
see the things we do
- We do. baby
- BACKUP SINGERS: Baby
In the middle of the night
In my dreams
I know I'm gonna be
with you. so I take my time
In the middle of the night
Baby. let the games begin
Let the games begin
Are you ready for it?
Baby. let the games begin
Let the games begin
Are you ready for it?
Baby. let the games begin
Let the games begin
Are you ready for it?
This ain't for the best
My reputation's
never been worse. so
You must like me for me
We can't make
Any promises now
Can we. babe?
Um. dois. três!
Dive bar on the East Side
Where you at?
Phone lights up
my nightstand in the black
Come here
You can meet me in the back
Dark jeans and your Nikes
Look at you
Damn
Never seen that color blue
Just think of the fun things
we could do
'Cause I like you
This ain't for the best
My reputation's
never been worse. so
You must like me for me
Yeah. I want you
We can't make
Any promises now
Can we. babe?
But you can
make me a drink
Is it cool
that I said all that?
Is it chill
that you're in my head?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
Delicate
Is it cool
that I said all that?
Is it too soon
to do this yet?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
Isn't it?
Isn't it? Isn't it?
Delicate
Third floor
on the West Side. me and you
Handsome. you're a mansion
with a view
Do the girls back home
touch you like I do?
Long night. with your hands
up in my hair
Echoes of your footsteps
on the stairs
Stay here. honey
I don't wanna share
'Cause I like you
This ain't for the best
My reputation's
never been worse. so
You must like me for me
Yeah. I want you
We can't make
Any promises now
Can we. babe?
But you can
make me a drink
Is it cool
that I said all that?
Is it chill
that you're in my head?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
Delicate
Is it cool
that I said all that?
Is it too soon
to do this yet?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
Isn't it?
Isn't it? Isn't it?
Delicate
Sometimes I wonder
when you sleep
Are you ever
dreaming of me?
Sometimes when I look
into your eyes
I pretend you're mine
All the damn time
'Cause I like you
Is it cool
that I said all that?
Is it chill
that you're in my head?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
Yeah. I want you
Is it cool
that I said all that?
Is it too soon
to do this yet?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
'Cause I like you
Is it cool
that I said all that?
Is it chill
that you're in my head?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
Yeah. I want you
Is it cool
that I said all that?
Is it too soon
to do this yet?
'Cause I know
that it's delicate
Isn't it?
Delicate
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
Lord. save me
My drug is my baby
I'll be using
for the rest of my life
I've been breaking hearts
a long time
And toying
with them older guys
Just playthings
for me to use
Something happened
for the first time
In the darkest little paradise
Shaking. pacing
I just need you
For you
I would cross the line
I would waste my time
I would lose my mind
They say. "She's gone
too far this time"
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
Lord. save me
My drug is my baby
I'll be using
for the rest of my life
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
Lord. save me
My drug is my baby
I'll be using
for the rest of my life
I get so high.
Every time you're
Every time you're loving me
You're loving me
Trip of my life.
Every time you're
Every time
you're touching me
You're touching me
I get so high.
Trip of my life.
Every time you're
Every time you're loving me
Lord. save me
My drug is my baby
I'll be using
for the rest of my life
Using for the rest
of my life
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
Doing it right. no
Lord. save me
My drug is my baby
I'll be using
for the rest of my life
Life.
Don't blame me
Love made me crazy
If it doesn't
You ain't doing it right
- You ain't doing it right
- Lord. save me
My drug is my baby
I'll be using
- For the rest of my life
- I'll be using
I'll be using
Every time you're
Every time you're loving me
You're loving me
Lord. save me
My drug is my baby
I'll be using
for the rest of my life
Don't blame me
for what you made me do
I don't like your little games
Don't like your tilted stage
The role you made me play
Of the fool
No. I don't like you
I don't like
your perfect crime
How you laugh when you lie
You said the gun was mine
Isn't cool
No. I don't like you
But I got smarter
I got harder
in the nick of time
Honey. I rose up
from the dead
I do it all the time
I've got a list of names
And yours is in red Underlined
I check it once
Then I check it twice!
Ooh. look what
you made me do
Look what you made me do
Look what you just made me do
Look what you just made me
Ooh. look what you made me do
Look what you made me do
Look what
you just made me do
I don't like
your kingdom keys
They once belonged to me
You asked me
for a place to sleep
Locked me out
and threw a feast
- What?
- The world moves on
Another day
Another drama. drama
But not for me. not for me
All I think about is karma
And then the world moves on
But one thing's for sure
Maybe I got mine
But you'll all get yours
But I got smarter
I got harder
in the nick of time
Honey. I rose up
from the dead
I do it all the time
I've got a list of names
And yours is in red Underlined
I check it once
Then I check it twice!
Ooh. look what you made me do
Look what you made me do
Look what you just made me do
Look what you just made me
Ooh. look what you made me do
Look what you made me do
Look what you just made me do
I don't trust nobody
and nobody trusts me
I'll be the actress
starring in your bad dreams
I don't trust nobody
and nobody trusts me
I'll be the actress
starring in your bad dreams
I don't trust nobody
and nobody trusts me
I'll be the actress
starring in your bad dreams
I don't trust nobody
and nobody trusts me
I'll be the actress
starring in your bad dreams
"I'm sorry
"But the old Taylor can't
come to the phone right now"
"Why?"
"'Cause she's dead!"
Ooh. look what
you made me do
Look what you made me do
Look what
you just made me do
Look what you just made me
Ooh. look what
you made me do
Look what you made me do
Look what
you just made me do
Look what you just made me
Ooh. look what
you made me do
Look what you made me do
Look what
you just made me do
Look what you just made me
Ooh. look what
you made me do
Look what you made me do
Look what
you just made me do
Look what you made me do
There I was again tonight
Forcing laughter
Faking smiles
Same old tired. lonely place
Walls of insincerity
Shifting eyes and vacancy
Vanished when I saw your face
All I can say is it was
Enchanting to meet you
Your eyes whispered
"Have we met?"
Across the room
Your silhouette
Starts to make its way to me
The playful
conversation starts
Counter all
your quick remarks
Like passing notes
in secrecy
And it was
Enchanting to meet you
All I can say is I was
This night is sparklin'
Don't you let it go
I'm wonderstruck
Blushin' all the way home
I'll spend forever
wonderin' if you knew
I was enchanted to meet you
This is me praying that
This was the very first page
Not where the storyline ends
My thoughts
will echo your name
Until I see you again
These are the words
I held back
As I was leaving too soon
I was enchanted
to meet you
Please. don't be in love
with someone else
Please. don't have
somebody waiting on you
Please. don't be in love
with someone else
Please. don't have
somebody waiting on you
This night is sparklin'
Don't you let it go
I'm wonderstruck
Blushin' all the way home
I'll spend forever
Wonderin' if you knew
This night is flawless
Don't you let it go
I'm wonderstruck
Dancing around all alone
I'll spend forever
wonderin' if you knew
I was enchanted to meet you
Please. don't be in love
With someone else
Please. don't have
somebody waiting on you
MUITA COISA ACONTECENDO NO MOMENTO
It feels like
a perfect night
To dress up like hipsters
And make fun of our exes
It feels like
a perfect night
For breakfast at midnight
To fall in love with strangers
Yeah
We're happy. free
Confused and lonely
At the same time
It's miserable and magical
Yeah
Tonight's the night
When we forget
about the deadlines
It's time
I don't know about you
But I'm feeling 22
Everything will be all right if
You keep me next to you
You don't know about me
But I'll bet you want to
Everything will be all right if
We just keep dancing
like we're
It feels like
one of those nights
This place is too crowded
Too many cool kids
"Who is Taylor Swift
anyway? Ew"
It seems like
one of those nights
We ditch the whole scene
And end up dreaming
instead of sleeping
Yeah
We're happy. free
Confused and lonely
In the best way
It's miserable and magical
Yeah
Tonight's the night
When we forget
about the heartbreaks
It's time
- Hey!
- I don't know about you
But I'm feeling 22
Everything will be all right if
You keep me next to you
You don't know about me
But I'll bet you want to
Everything will be all right if
We just keep dancing
like we're
It feels
like one of those nights
We ditch the whole scene
It feels
like one of those nights
We won't be sleeping
It feels like
one of those nights
You look like bad news
I gotta have you
Ooh. ooh
Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah
Yeah. yeah
I don't know about you
But I'm feeling 22
Everything will be all right if
You keep me next to you
You don't know about me
You don't know
about me
But I'll bet you want to
Everything will be all right if
We just keep dancing
like we're
It feels like
one of those nights
We ditch the whole scene
It feels
like one of those nights
We won't be sleeping
It feels like
one of those nights
You look like bad news
I gotta have you
I remember when we broke up
the first time
Saying. "This is it
I've had enough"
'Cause like
We hadn't seen each other
in a month
When you said
you needed space. what?
Then you come around again
and say
"Baby. I miss you
and I swear I'm gonna change
"Trust me"
Remember how that lasted
for a day?
I say. "I hate you"
We break up
You call me. "I love you"
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
We called it off again
last night but
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
This time I'm telling you
I'm telling you
We are never ever ever
getting back together
You go talk to your friends
Talk to my friends. talk to me
But we are never ever ever
ever getting back together
Like. ever
I'm really gonna miss you
picking fights
And me falling for it
Screaming that I'm right
And you would hide away
and find your peace of mind
With some indie record
that's much cooler than mine
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
You called me up again
tonight but
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
This time. I'm telling you
I'm telling you
We are never ever ever
getting back together
You go talk
to your friends
Talk to my friends
Talk to me
You talk to me
But we are never ever ever
ever getting back together
- Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
- Yeah
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
Yeah
No
I used to think
that we were forever ever
And I used to say
never say never
So he calls me up
And he's like
"I still love you"
And I'm like. I'm just
I mean this is exhausting
You know?
Like. we are never
getting back together
Like. ever
No
We are never ever ever
Getting back together
You go talk to your friends
Talk to my friends
Talk to me
But we are
Never ever ever ever
getting back together
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
- No
- Getting back together
We
Ooh ooh ooh ooh ooh
No. no
You go talk to your friends
Talk to my friends
talk to me
But we are never ever ever
ever getting back together
Once upon a time
A few mistakes ago
I was in your sights
You got me alone
You found me. you found me
You found me
I guess you didn't care
and I guess I liked that
And when I fell hard
You took a step back
Without me. without me
Without me
And he's long gone
when he's next to me
And I realize
the blame is on me
'Cause I knew you were
trouble when you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places
I'd never been
Till you put me down.
I knew you were trouble
when you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places
I'd never been
Now I'm lying
on the cold hard ground
Trouble. trouble. trouble
And the saddest fear
Comes creeping in
That you never loved me
Or her. or anyone. or anything
- Yeah
- I knew you were trouble
When you walked in
So shame on me now
Flew me to places
I'd never been
Never been
Till you put me down.
I knew you were trouble
when you walked in
Knew it right there
Flew me to places
I'd never been
Now I'm lying
on the cold hard ground
Trouble. trouble
- Trouble
Trouble. trouble. trouble
I knew you were trouble
when you walked in
Trouble. trouble. trouble
I knew you were trouble
when you walked in
Trouble. trouble. trouble
LA. estão gostando
da Era Red até agora?
Que bom. Fico feliz de ouvir isso.
porque tem mais uma música
que eu estava querendo cantar
do álbum "Red".
se. por acaso.
tiverem uns dez minutos sobrando.
I walked through
the door with you
The air was cold
But something 'bout it
felt like home somehow
And I left my scarf there
at your sister's house
And you've still got it
in your drawer. even now
Your sweet disposition
and my wide-eyed gaze
We're singing in the car
Getting lost upstate
Autumn leaves falling down
like pieces into place
And I can picture it
after all these days
And I know
it's long gone and
That magic's not here
no more
And I might be okay
But I'm not fine at all
'Cause there we are again
on that little town street
You almost ran the red
'Cause you were
lookin' over at me
Wind in my hair. I was there
I remember it
all too well
Photo album on the counter
Your cheeks were turning red
You used to be a little kid
With glasses
in a twin-sized bed
Your mother's telling
stories 'bout you
On the tee-ball team
You taught me 'bout your past
Thinking your future
was me
And you were tossing me
the car keys
"Fuck the patriarchy"
Keychain on the ground
We were always
skipping town
And I was thinking
on the drive down
Any time now
He's gonna say it's love
You never called it
what it was
Till we were dead and gone
and buried
Check the pulse and come back
Swearing it's the same
After three months
in the grave
And then you wondered
where it went to
As I reached for you
But all I felt was shame
And you held
my lifeless frame
And I know
it's long gone and
There was nothing else
I could do
And I forget about you
long enough
To forget why I needed to
'Cause there we are again
in the middle of the night
We're dancing
'round the kitchen
In the refrigerator light
Down the stairs. I was there
I remember it all too well
And there we are again
when nobody had to know
You kept me like a secret
but I kept you like an oath
Sacred prayer and we'd swear
To remember it
All too well. yeah
Well. maybe we got
lost in translation
Maybe I asked for too much
But maybe this thing
was a masterpiece
Till you tore it all up
Running scared. I was there
I remember it all too well
And you call me up again
Just to break me
like a promise
So casually cruel in
the name of "being honest"
I'm a crumpled up
piece of paper lying here
'Cause I remember it
all. all. all
They say all's well
that ends well
But I'm in a new hell
Every time
you double-cross my mind
You said if we had
been closer in age
Maybe it would have been fine
And that made me want to die
The idea you had of me
Who was she?
A never-needy
ever-lovely jewel
Whose shine reflects on you
Not weeping
in a party bathroom
Some actress asking me
what happened. you
That's what happened. you
You who charmed my dad
with self-effacing jokes
Sipping coffee like
you're on a late-night show
But then he watched me watch
the front door all night
Willing you to come
And he said
"It's supposed to be fun
"Turning 21"
Time won't fly
It's like
I'm paralyzed by it
I'd like to be
my old self again
But I'm still
trying to find it
After plaid shirt days
And nights when
you made me your own
Now you mail back my things
and I walk home alone
But you keep my old scarf
from that very first week
'Cause it reminds you
of innocence
And it smells like me
You can't get rid of it
'Cause you remember it
All too well. yeah
'Cause there we are again
when I loved you so
Back before you lost
The one real thing
you've ever known
It was rare. I was there
I remember it all too well
Wind in my hair
You were there
You remember it all
Down the stairs
You were there
You remember it all
It was rare. I was there
I remember it all too well
And I was never good
at telling jokes
But the punch line goes
"I'll get older
But your lovers stay my age"
From when your Brooklyn
broke my skin and bones
I'm a soldier who's
returning half her weight
And did the twin flame
bruise paint you blue?
Just between us
Did the love affair
maim you. too?
'Cause in this city's
barren cold
I still remember
the first fall of snow
And how it glistened
as it fell
I remember it all too well
Just between us
Did the love affair
maim you
All too well?
Just between us
Do you remember it
All too well?
Just between us
- I remember it
- Just between us
- All too well
- Wind in my hair
- I was there. I was there
- I was there
Down the stairs
I was there. I was there
I was there
Sacred prayer
I was there. I was there
It was rare
You remember it
- All too well
- Wind in my hair
- I was there. I was there
- I was there
Down the stairs
I was there. I was there
I was there
Sacred prayer
I was there. I was there
It was rare
You remember it
Wind in my hair
I was there. I was there
Down the stairs
Sacred prayer
I was there. I was there
It was rare
You remember it
I'm doing good
I'm on some new shit
Been saying "yes"
instead of "no"
I thought I saw you
at the bus stop
I didn't though
I hit the ground running
each night
I hit the Sunday matinee
You know the greatest films
of all time were never made
I guess you never know
Never know
And if you wanted me
You really should've showed
And if you never bleed
You're never gonna grow
And it's all right now
But we were something
Don't you think so?
Roaring twenties
Tossing pennies in the pool
And if my wishes came true
It would've been you
In my defense. I have none
For never leaving
well enough alone
But it would've been fun
If you would've been the one
Ooh
I have this dream
you're doing cool shit
Having adventures on your own
You meet some woman
on the Internet
And take her home
We never painted
by the numbers. baby
But we were making it count
You know the greatest loves
of all time are over now
I guess you never know
Never know
And it's another day
Waking up alone
But we were something
Don't you think so?
Roaring twenties
Tossing pennies in the pool
And if my wishes came true
It would've been you
In my defense. I have none
For never leaving
well enough alone
But it would've been fun
If you would've been the one
Hey. yeah-yeah
I persist and resist
the temptation to ask you
If one thing
had been different
Would everything
be different today?
We were something
Don't you think so?
Rosé flowing
with your chosen family
And it would've been sweet
If it could've been me
In my defense. I have none
For digging up
the grave another time
But it would've been fun
If you would've been
the one
Ooh
Então. trouxemos
o chalé de "Folklore" para LA.
Tenho muito orgulho
do álbum "Folklore"
e comecei...
Obrigada.
Eu visualizei esse álbum
num cenário de floresta.
em um chalé imaginário.
Na minha fantasia.
na minha imaginação.
não sou uma millennial solitária
coberta de pelos de gato.
assistindo 700 horas de TV por dia.
Na minha imaginação. sou...
uma dama vitoriana campestre.
que vaga pela floresta.
segurando um castiçal e...
coletando penas pra caneta-tinteiro
pra escrever em pergaminho.
Era uma coisa toda.
Foi assim que eu me imaginei
ao compor "Folklore".
E eu pensei em fazer
outras coisas diferentes.
Talvez eu devesse
tentar criar personagens
e fazer os personagens
se apaixonarem e terminarem e...
Um dos meus personagens favoritos é...
Criei "Teenage Love Triangle".
triângulo amoroso adolescente.
O personagem catalisador é o James.
e ele realmente estraga tudo
com o amor de sua vida.
e tem que se desculpar com ela.
e tentar consertar.
e. resumindo. o nome dela é "Betty".
Betty. I won't
make assumptions
About why you switched
your homeroom
But I think
it's 'cause of me
Betty. one time I was riding
on my skateboard
When I passed your house
It's like
I couldn't breathe
You heard the rumors
from Inez
You can't believe
a word she says
Most times
But this time it was true
The worst thing
that I ever did
Was what I did to you
But if I just showed up
at your party
Would you have me?
Would you want me?
Would you tell me
to go fuck myself
Or lead me to the garden?
In the garden
would you trust me
If I told you
it was just a summer thing?
I'm only 17
I don't know anything
but I know I miss you
Betty. I know
where it all went wrong
Your favorite song
was playing
From the far side
of the gym
I was nowhere to be found
I hate the crowds
You know that
Plus. I saw you dance
with him
You heard the rumors
from Inez
You can't believe
a word she says
Most times
But this time it was true
The worst thing
that I ever did
Was what I did to you
But if I just showed up
at your party
Would you have me?
Would you want me?
Would you tell me
to go fuck myself
Or lead me to the garden?
In the garden
would you trust me
If I told you
it was just a summer thing?
I'm only 17
I don't know anything
but I know I miss you
I was walking home
on broken cobblestones
Just thinking of you
when she pulled up
Like a figment
of my worst intentions
She said
"James. get in. let's drive"
Those days turned into nights
Slept next to her but
I dreamt of you
all summer long
Betty. I'm here
on your doorstep
And I planned it out
for weeks now
But it's finally
sinking in
Betty. right now
is the last time
I can dream
about what happens
When you see my face again
The only thing I wanna do
Is make it up to you
So. I showed up at your party
Yeah. I showed up
at your party
Will you have me?
Will you love me?
Will you kiss me
on the porch
In front of
all your stupid friends?
If you kiss me
Will it be
just like I dreamed it?
Will it patch
your broken wings?
I'm only 17
I don't know anything
But I know I miss you
Standing in your cardigan
Kissing in my car again
Stopped at a streetlight
You know I miss you
Rebekah rode up
on the afternoon train
It was sunny
Her saltbox house
on the coast
Took her mind off St. Louis
Bill was the heir
to the Standard Oil name
And money
And the town said
"How did a middle-class
divorcée do it?"
The wedding was charming
If a little gauche
There's only so far
new money goes
They picked out a home
And called it "Holiday House"
Their parties were tasteful
If a little loud
The doctor had told him
to settle down
It must have been her fault
his heart gave out
And they said
"There goes the last great
American dynasty
"Who knows
If she never showed up
"What could've been
"There goes
the maddest woman
"This town has ever seen
"She had a marvelous time
ruining everything"
Rebekah gave up on
the Rhode Island set forever
Flew in all her Bitch Pack
friends from the city
Filled the pool
with champagne
And swam with the big names
And blew through the money
on the boys and the ballet
And losing on
card game bets with Dalí
And they said
"There goes the last
great American dynasty
"Who knows
If she never showed up
"What could've been
Amo vocês.
"There goes
the most shameless woman
"This town has ever seen
"She had a marvelous time
ruining everything"
They say
she was seen on occasion
Pacing the rocks. staring
out at the midnight sea
And in a feud
with her neighbor
She stole his dog
and dyed it key lime green
Fifty years is a long time
Holiday House sat quietly
on that beach
Free of women with madness
Their men and bad habits
And then it was bought by me
Who knows. if I never
showed up what could've been
There goes the loudest woman
this town has ever seen
I had a marvelous time
ruining everything
Ruining everything
A marvelous time
I had a marvelous time
Salt air
And the rust on your door
I never needed anything more
Whispers
Of "Are you sure?"
"Never have I ever before"
But I can see us
Lost in the memory
August slipped away
into a moment in time
'Cause it was never mine
And I can see us
twisted in bedsheets
August sipped away
Like a bottle of wine
'Cause you were
never mine. mine
Your back
Beneath the sun
Wishing I could
write my name on it
Will you call
When you're back at school?
I remember thinking
I had you
But I can see us
Lost in the memory
August slipped away
into a moment in time
'Cause it was never mine
And I can see us
twisted in bedsheets
August sipped away
Like a bottle of wine
'Cause you were never mine
Mine
Back when we were still
changing for the better
Wanting was enough
For me. it was enough
To live for the hope
of it all
Cancel plans
just in case you'd call
And say
"Meet me behind the mall"
So much for summer love
and saying "us"
'Cause you weren't mine
to lose
You weren't mine to lose
No
But I can see us
Lost in the memory
August slipped away
into a moment in time
'Cause it was never mine
And I can see us
twisted in bedsheets
August sipped away
Like a bottle of wine
'Cause you were
never mine. mine
'Cause you were never mine
Never mine
But do you remember?
Remember when I pulled up
And said. "Get in the car"
And then canceled my plans
Just in case you'd call?
Back when I was living
for the hope of it all
For the hope of it all
"Meet me behind the mall"
Remember when I pulled up
And said. "Get in the car"
And then canceled my plans
Just in case you'd call?
Back when I was living
for the hope of it all
For the hope of it all
"Meet me behind the mall"
Remember when I pulled up
And said. "Get in the car"
And then canceled my plans
Just in case you'd call?
Back when I was living
for the hope of it all
For the hope of it all
- For the hope of it all
And you wanna scream
Don't call me "kid"
Don't call me "baby"
Look at this godforsaken mess
That you made me
You showed me colors
you know
I can't see
with anyone else
Don't call me "kid"
Don't call me "baby"
Look at this idiotic fool
you made me
You taught me
a secret language
I can't speak
with anyone else
Don't call me "kid"
Don't call me "baby"
Look at this
godforsaken mess
That you made me
You showed me colors
you know
I can't see with anyone else
Don't call me "kid"
Don't call me "baby"
Look at this idiotic fool
you made me
You taught me
a secret language
I can't speak
with anyone else
And you know damn well
For you I would ruin myself
A million little times
That's the thing
about illicit affairs
We gather here
We line up weeping
in a sunlit room
And if I'm on fire
You'll be made
of ashes. too
Even on my worst day
Did I deserve. babe
All the hell you gave me?
'Cause I loved you
I swear I loved you
Till my dying day
I didn't have it in myself
to go with grace
And you're the hero
flying around saving face
And if I'm dead to you
Why are you at the wake?
Cursing my name
Wishing I stayed
Look at how my tears ricochet
We gather stones
Never knowing
what they'll mean
Some to throw
Some to make a diamond ring
You know I didn't want to
Have to haunt you
But what a ghostly scene
You wear the same jewels
That I gave you
As you bury me
I didn't have it in myself
to go with grace
'Cause when I'd fight
You used to tell me
I was brave
And if I'm dead to you
Why are you at the wake?
Cursing my name
Wishing I stayed
Look at how
my tears ricochet
And I can go
anywhere I want
Anywhere I want
Just not home
And you can aim
for my heart. go for blood
But you would still miss me
in your bones
And I still talk to you
When I'm screaming
at the sky
And when you can't
sleep at night
You hear
my stolen lullabies
I didn't have it in myself
to go with grace
And so the battleships
will sink beneath the waves
You had to kill me
But it killed you
just the same
Cursing my name
Wishing I stayed
You turned into
your worst fears
And you're tossing out blame
Drunk on this pain
Crossing out the good years
And you're cursing my name
Wishing I stayed
Look at how
my tears ricochet
Midnight
You come and pick me up
No headlights
Long drive
Could end in burning flames
or paradise
Fade into view.
It's been a while since
I have even heard from you
Heard from you
I should just tell you
to leave 'cause I
Know exactly
where it leads. but I
Watch us go 'round
and 'round each time
You got that James Dean
daydream look in your eye
And I got that red lip
classic thing that you like
And when we go crashing down
We come back every time
'Cause we never go
out of style
We never go out of style
You got that long hair
Slicked back. white T-shirt
And I got that good girl faith
And a tight little skirt
And when we go crashing down
We come back every time
'Cause we never go
out of style
We never go out of style
Take me home
Just take me home
Yeah
Ooh. ooh.
Out of style
You got that James Dean
daydream look in your eye
And I got that red lip
classic thing that you like
I got that thing
that you like
And when we go crashing down
And when we go
We come back every time
We never go out of style
Nice to meet you
Where you been?
I could show you
incredible things
Magic. madness. heaven. sin
Saw you there
and I thought
"My God
Look at that face
"You look like
my next mistake
"Love's a game. wanna play?"
Ayy
New money. suit and tie
I can read you
like a magazine
Ain't it funny? Rumors fly
And I know you heard
about me
So. hey. let's be friends
I'm dying to see
how this one ends
Grab your passport
and my hand
I can make the bad guys good
for a weekend
So it's gonna be forever
Or it's gonna
go down in flames
You can tell me
when it's over.
If the high
was worth the pain
Got a long list of ex-lovers
They'll tell you I'm insane
'Cause you know
I love the players
And you love the game
'Cause we're young
and we're reckless
We'll take this
way too far
It'll leave you
breathless.
Or with a nasty scar
Got a long list of ex-lovers
They'll tell you I'm insane
But I've got
a blank space. baby
And I'll write your name
Cherry lips. crystal skies
I could show you
incredible things
Stolen kisses. pretty lies
You're the King. baby
I'm your Queen
Find out what you want
Be that girl for a month
Wait. the worst
is yet to come
No
Screaming. crying
Perfect storms
I can make
all the tables turn
Rose garden
filled with thorns
Keep you
second-guessing like
"My God. who is she?"
I get drunk on jealousy
But you'll come back
each time you leave
'Cause. darling
I'm a nightmare
Dressed like a daydream
So it's gonna be forever
Or it's gonna go
down in flames
You can tell me
when it's over.
If the high
was worth the pain
Got a long list
of ex-lovers
They'll tell you I'm insane
'Cause you know
I love the players
And you love the game
'Cause we're young
and we're reckless
We'll take this way too far
It'll leave you
breathless.
Or with a nasty scar
Got a long list
of ex-lovers
They'll tell you I'm insane
But I've got
a blank space. baby
And I'll write your name
Boys only want love
if it's torture
Don't say I didn't
Say I didn't warn ya
Boys only want love
if it's torture
Don't say I didn't
Say I didn't warn ya
So it's gonna be forever
Or it's gonna go
down in flames
You can tell me
when it's over
Over
If the high
was worth the pain
Got a long list
of ex-lovers
They'll tell you
I'm insane
'Cause you know
I love the players
And you love the game
'Cause we're young
and we're reckless
Yeah
We'll take this way too far
Ooh
It'll leave you
breathless.
- Or with a nasty scar
- Leave a nasty scar
Got a long list
of ex-lovers
They'll tell you I'm insane
But I've got
a blank space. baby
And I'll write your name
I stay out too late
Got nothing in my brain
- That's what people say
- BACKUP SINGERS: -
I go on too many dates
But I can't make them stay
At least
that's what people say
- That's what people say
- BACKUP SINGERS: -
But I keep cruising
Can't stop
Won't stop moving
It's like I got this music
In my mind
Saying "It's gonna be all right"
'Cause the players gonna
play. play. play. play. play
And the haters gonna
hate. hate. hate. hate. hate
I'm just gonna shake
Shake. shake. shake. shake
I shake it off
Heart-breakers gonna break
Break. break. break. break
And the fakers gonna fake
Fake. fake. fake. fake
I'm just gonna shake
Shake. shake. shake. shake
I shake it off
I never miss a beat
I'm lightning on my feet
And that's what they don't see
That's what they don't see
I'm dancing on my own
Dancing on my own
I make the moves up as I go
Moves up as I go
And that's what
they don't know
That's what they don't know
But I keep cruising
Can't stop
Won't stop grooving
It's like I got this music
In my mind
Saying "It's gonna be all right"
'Cause the players gonna play
Play. play. play. play
And the haters gonna hate
Hate. hate. hate. hate
I'm just gonna shake
Shake. shake. shake. shake
I shake it off
Heart-breakers gonna break
Break. break. break. break
And the fakers gonna fake
Fake. fake. fake. fake. fake
I'm just gonna shake
Shake. shake. shake. shake
I shake it off
Shake it off. I shake it off
I. I. I shake it off
I shake it off
Hey. hey. hey
Just think while you've been
getting down and out
About the liars
and the dirty. dirty cheats
Of the world
You could've been getting
down to this sick beat
My ex-man brought
his new girlfriend
She's like. "My God!"
but I'm just gonna shake
And to the fella over there
with the hella good hair
Won't you come on over. baby?
We can shake. shake. shake
Yeah
'Cause the players
gonna play
Play. play. play. play
And the haters gonna hate
- Hate. hate. hate. hate
- Haters gonna hate
I'm just gonna shake
Shake. shake. shake. shake
I shake it off
Heart-breakers gonna break
Break. break. break. break
And the fakers gonna fake
Fake. fake. fake. fake
I'm just gonna shake
Shake. shake. shake. shake
I shake it off
Shake it off. I shake it off
I. I. I shake it off
I shake it off
Shake it off
I. I. I shake it off
I shake it off
You've got to
Shake it off. I shake it off
I. I. I shake it off
I shake it off
ESTÁDIO SOFI
'Cause. baby
Now we got bad blood
You know
it used to be mad love
So take a look
what you've done
'Cause. baby
Now we got bad blood
Hey
Now we got problems
And I don't think
we can solve them
You made a really deep cut
And. baby
Now we got bad blood
Hey
It's so sad to
think about the good times
You and I
'Cause. baby
Now we got bad blood
You know
it used to be mad love
So take a look
what you've done
'Cause. baby
Now we got bad blood
Hey
Now we got problems
And I don't think
we can solve them
You made a really deep cut
And. baby
Now we got bad blood
Hey
Band-Aids don't fix
bullet holes
You say sorry just for show
If you live like that
You live with ghosts
Band-Aids don't fix
bullet holes
You say sorry just for show
If you live like that
You live with ghosts
Ooh
If you love like that
Blood runs cold
'Cause. baby
Now we got bad blood
You know it used to be
- Mad love
- BACKUP SINGERS: Mad love
So take a look
what you've done
' Cause. baby. now we got
Bad blood Hey
Now we got problems
And I don't think
we can solve them
You made a really deep cut
And. baby
Now we got bad blood
- Now we got bad
- 'Cause. baby. now
- We got bad blood
- Blood
You know it used to be
- Mad love
So take a look
what you've done
Look what you've done
'Cause. baby. now we got
Bad Blood Hey
Now we got problems
And I don't think
we can solve them
You made a really deep cut
And. baby
Now we got bad blood
Hey
Bem-vindos ao set acústico!
Quando sonhei
com a ideia do The Eras Tour.
pensei que seria divertido
voltar a todas as fases diferentes
que tive musicalmente. porque fiz...
fiz um pouco de tudo.
Vocês têm sido muito legais comigo.
me deixando explorar gêneros
e sair das categorias que são criadas
na indústria da música.
E é só por causa de vocês
que eu posso fazer isso.
Então. obrigada.
porque é muito bacana.
É muito bacana tocar. experimentar
e crescer como artista.
Quero tocar uma música para agradecer
às pessoas que gostavam de mim
quando eu era adolescente compondo
para o show de talentos do nono ano.
I was riding shotgun
With my hair undone
In the front seat of his car
He's got a one-hand feel
On the steering wheel
The other on my heart
I look around
Turn the radio down
He says
"Baby. is something wrong?"
I say. "Nothing
I was just thinking
"How we don't have a song"
And he says
Our song is
the slamming screen door
Sneakin' out late
Tapping on your window
When we're on the phone
and you talk real slow
'Cause it's late
and your mama don't know
Our song
is the way you laugh
The first date
"Man. I didn't kiss her
and I should have"
And when I got home
'fore I said. "Amen"
Asking God
if he could play it again
I was walking up
The front porch steps
After everything that day
Had gone all wrong
And been trampled on
And lost and thrown away
Got to the hallway
Well. on my way
To my lovin' bed
I almost didn't notice
All the roses
And the note that said
Our song is
the slamming screen door
Sneakin' out late
Tapping on your window
When we're on the phone
and you talk real slow
'Cause it's late
and your mama don't know
Our song
is the way you laugh
The first date
"Man. I didn't kiss her
and I should have"
And when I got home
'fore I said. "Amen"
Asking God
if he could play it again
I've heard every album
Listened to the radio
Waited for something
to come along
That was as good as our song
'Cause our song is
the slamming screen door
Sneakin' out late
Tapping on his window
When we're on the phone
and he talks real slow
'Cause it's late
and his mama don't know
Our song
is the way he laughs
The first date
"Man. I didn't kiss him
and I should have"
And when I got home
'fore I said. "Amen"
Asking God
if he could play it again
Play it again
Yeah
yeah
I was riding shotgun
With my hair undone
In the front seat of his car
I grabbed a pen
And an old napkin
And I wrote down our song
Summer went away
Still the yearning stays
I play it cool
with the best of them
I wait patiently
He's gonna notice me
It's okay
We're the best of friends
Anyway
I hear it in your voice
You're smoking
with your boys
I touch my phone
as if it's your face
I didn't choose this town
I dream of getting out
There's just one
who could make me stay
All my days
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
I waited ages
to see you there
I search the party
of better bodies
Just to learn
that you never cared
You're on your own. kid
You always have been
I see the great escape
So long. Daisy May
I picked the petals
He loves me not
Something different bloomed
Writing in my room
I play my songs
in the parking lot
I'll run away
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
I called a taxi
to take me there
I search the party
of better bodies
Just to learn
that my dreams aren't rare
You're on your own. kid
You always have been
From sprinkler splashes
to fireplace ashes
I gave my blood. sweat
and tears for this
I hosted parties
and starved my body
Like I'd be saved
by a perfect kiss
The jokes weren't funny
I took the money
My friends from home
don't know what to say
I looked around
in a blood-soaked gown
And I saw something
they can't take away
'Cause there were pages turned
With the bridges burned
Everything you lose
is a step you take
So make
the friendship bracelets
Take the moment and taste it
You've got no reason
to be afraid
You're on your own. kid
Yeah. you can face this
You always have been
Amo vocês.
Meet me at midnight
whoa
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
Staring at the ceiling
with you
You don't ever
say too much
You don't really read into
My melancholia
- I've been under scrutiny
- BACKUP SINGERS: Yeah. yeah
- You handle it beautifully
All this shit is new to me
Yeah. yeah
I feel the lavender haze
creeping up on me
Surreal
I'm damned if I do give
a damn what people say
No deal
The 1950s shit
they want from me
I just wanna stay
in that lavender haze
whoa
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
All they keep asking me
Is if I'm gonna be your bride
The only kinda girl they see
Only kinda girl they see
Is a one-night or a wife
- I find it dizzying
- BACKUP SINGERS: Yeah. yeah
They're bringing up
my history
Yeah. yeah
But you weren't
even listening
Yeah. yeah
Ooh ooh ooh
I feel the lavender haze
creeping up on me
Surreal
I'm damned if I do give
a damn what people say
No deal
The 1950s shit
they want from me
I just wanna stay
in that lavender haze
- That lavender haze
- BACKUP SINGERS: -whoa
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
Talk your talk and go viral
I just need this love spiral
Get it off your chest
Get it off my desk
Talk your talk and go viral
I just need this love spiral
Get it off your chest
Get it off my desk
- I feel
The lavender haze
creeping up on me
Surreal
I'm damned if I do give
a damn what people say
- No deal
The 1950s shit
they want from me
I just wanna stay
in that lavender haze
- Whoa
- Get it off your chest
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa
- Get it off my desk
That lavender haze
I just wanna stay
in that lavender haze
I have this thing
where I get older
But just never wiser
Midnights become
my afternoons
When my depression
works the graveyard shift
All of the people
I've ghosted
stand there in the room
I should not be left
to my own devices
They come with prices
and vices
I end up in crisis
Tale as old as time
I wake up screaming
from dreaming
One day
I'll watch as you're leaving
'Cause you got tired
of my scheming
For the last time
It's me. hi
I'm the problem. it's me
At teatime. everybody agrees
I'll stare directly
at the sun
But never in the mirror
It must be exhausting always
rooting for the anti-hero
Sometimes. I feel like
everybody is a sexy baby
And I'm a monster on the hill
Too big to hang out
Slowly lurching toward
your favorite city
Pierced through the heart
but never killed
Did you hear
my covert narcissism
I disguise as altruism
Like some kind
of congressman?
Tale as old as time
I wake up screaming
from dreaming
One day
I'll watch as you're leaving
And life will lose
all its meaning
For the last time
It's me. hi
I'm the problem. it's me
At teatime. everybody agrees
I'll stare directly
at the sun
But never in the mirror
It must be exhausting always
rooting for the anti-hero
I have this dream
My daughter-in-law kills me
for the money
She thinks I left them
in the will
The family gathers 'round
and reads it
And then someone
screams out
"She's laughing up at us
from hell"
It's me. hi
I'm the problem. it's me
Everybody agrees
It's me
- Hi
- I'm the problem. it's me
- At teatime
- Teatime
- Everybody agrees
I'll stare directly
at the sun
But never in the mirror
It must be exhausting always
rooting for the anti-hero
Rain
He wanted it comfortable
I wanted that pain
He wanted a bride
I was making my own name
Chasing that fame
He stayed the same
All of me changed
Like midnight
My town
was a wasteland
Full of cages. full of fences
Pageant queens
and big pretenders
But for some it was paradise
My boy was a montage
A slow motion. love potion
Jumping off things
in the ocean
I broke his heart
'cause he was nice
He was sunshine
I was midnight
Rain
He wanted it comfortable
I wanted that pain
He wanted a bride
I was making my own name
Chasing that fame
He stayed the same
All of me changed
Like midnight
It came like a postcard
Picture perfect shiny family
Holiday peppermint candy
But for him it's every day
So I peered through a window
A deep portal. time travel
All the love we unravel
And the life I gave away
'Cause he was sunshine
I was midnight rain
He wanted it comfortable
I wanted that pain
He wanted a bride
I was making my own name
Chasing that fame
He stayed the same
All of me changed
Like midnight
Rain
He wanted it comfortable
I wanted that pain
He wanted a bride
I was making my own name
Chasing that fame
He stayed the same
All of me changed
Like midnight
I guess sometimes we all get
Just what we wanted
And he never thinks of me
Except when I'm on TV
I guess sometimes we all get
Some kind of haunted
And I never think of him
Except on midnights like this
Midnights like this
Draw the cat eye
sharp enough to kill a man
You did some bad things
but I'm the worst of them
Sometimes I wonder which one
will be your last lie
They say looks can kill
and I might try
I don't dress for women
I don't dress for men
Lately I've been
dressing for revenge
I don't start shit. but
I can tell you how it ends
Don't get sad. get even
So on the weekends
I don't dress for friends
Lately I've been
dressing for revenge
She needed cold hard proof
so I gave her some
She had the envelope
Where you think
she got it from?
Now she gets the house
Gets the kids
Gets the pride
Picture me thick as thieves
with your ex-wife
And she looks so pretty
Driving in your Benz
Lately she's been
dressing for revenge
She don't start shit
But she can tell you
how it ends
Don't get sad. get even
So on the weekends
She don't dress for friends
Lately she's been
dressing for revenge
Ladies always rise above
Ladies know
what people want
Someone sweet
and kind and fun
The lady simply had enough
While he was doing lines
And crossing all of mine
Someone told
his white collar crimes
To the FBI
And I don't
dress for villains
Or for innocents
I'm on my vigilante shit again
I don't start shit. but
I can tell you how it ends
Don't get sad. get even
So on the weekends
I don't dress for friends
Lately I've been
dressing for revenge
Baby love. I think I've been
a little too kind
Didn't notice you walking
all over my peace of mind
In the shoes
I gave you as a present
Putting someone first
only works
When you're in their top five
And by the way
I'm going out tonight
Best believe
I'm still bejeweled
When I walk in the room
I can still make
the whole place shimmer
And when I meet the band
They ask
"Do you have a man?"
I could still say
"I don't remember"
Familiarity breeds contempt
Don't put me in the basement
When I want the penthouse
of your heart
Diamonds in my eyes
I polish up real
I polish up real nice
Nice
Baby boy. I think I've been
too good of a girl
Too good of a girl
Did all the extra credit
Then got graded on a curve
I think it's time
to teach some lessons
I made you my world
Have you heard?
I can reclaim the land
And I miss you
But I miss sparkling
Nice
Best believe
I'm still bejeweled
When I walk in the room
I can still make
the whole place shimmer
And when I meet the band
They ask
"Do you have a man?"
I could still say
"I don't remember"
Familiarity breeds contempt
Don't put me in the basement
When I want the penthouse
of your heart
Diamonds in my eyes
I polish up real
I polish up real nice
Nice
Sapphire tears on my face
Sadness became my whole sky
But some guy said
my aura's moonstone
Just 'cause he was high
And we're dancing all night
And you can try
To change my mind
But you might have
to wait in line
What's a girl gonna do?
A diamond's gotta shine
Best believe
I'm still bejeweled
When I walk in the room
I can still make
the whole place shimmer
- Shimmer
- And when I meet the band
They ask
"Do you have a man?
I could still say
"I don't remember"
Familiarity breeds contempt
Don't put me in the basement
When I want the penthouse
of your heart
Diamonds in my eyes
- I polish up real
- Nice
I polish up real nice
And we're dancing
all night
And you can try
To change my mind
But you might have
to wait in line
What's a girl gonna do?
I polish up nice
Best believe
I'm still bejeweled
When I walk in the room
I can still make
the whole place shimmer
Once upon a time
the planets and the fates
And all the stars aligned
You and I ended up
in the same room
At the same time
And the touch of a hand
lit the fuse
Of a chain reaction
of countermoves
To assess the equation of you
Checkmate. I couldn't lose
What if I told you
none of it was accidental?
And the first night
that you saw me
Nothing was gonna stop me
I laid the groundwork
and then just like clockwork
The dominoes
cascaded in a line
What if I told you
I'm a mastermind?
And now you're mine
It was all my design
'Cause I'm a mastermind
You see all the wisest women
had to do it this way
'Cause we were born to be
The pawn
in every lover's game
If you fail to plan
You plan to fail
Strategy sets the scene
for the tale
I'm the wind
in our free-flowing sails
And the liquor
in our cocktails
What if I told you
none of it was accidental?
And the first night
that you saw me
I knew I wanted your body
I laid the groundwork
and then just like clockwork
The dominoes
cascaded in a line
What if I told you
I'm a mastermind?
And now you're mine
It was all my design
'Cause I'm a mastermind
No one wanted to play
with me as a little kid
So I've been scheming
like a criminal ever since
To make them love me
and make it seem effortless
This is the first time I've
felt the need to confess
And I swear
I'm only cryptic
and Machiavellian
'Cause I care
So I told you none of it
was accidental
And the first night
that you saw me
Nothing was gonna stop me
I laid the groundwork
and then saw a wide smirk
On your face
You knew the entire time
You knew
that I'm a mastermind
And now you're mine
Yeah. all you did
was smile
'Cause I'm a mastermind
Vocês nos deram
o máximo de vocês hoje.
então me sinto culpada por pedir...
mas podemos ter o seu tempo
para mais uma música?
You're talking shit
for the hell of it
Addicted to betrayal
but you're relevant
You're terrified to look down
'Cause if you dare
You'll see the glare
Of everyone you burned
just to get there
It's coming back around
And I keep my side
of the street clean
You wouldn't know
what I mean
'Cause karma is my boyfriend
Karma is a god
Karma is the breeze
in my hair on the weekend
Karma's a relaxing thought
Aren't you envious
that for you it's not?
Sweet like honey
Karma is a cat
Purring in my lap
'cause it loves me
Flexing like
a goddamn acrobat
Me and karma vibe like that
Spiderboy. king of thieves
Weave your little webs
of opacity
My pennies made your crown
Trick me once. trick me twice
Don't you know that
cash ain't the only price?
It's coming back around
And I keep my side
of the street clean
You wouldn't know what I mean
'Cause karma is my boyfriend
Karma is a god
Karma is the breeze
in my hair on the weekend
Karma's a relaxing thought
Aren't you envious
that for you it's not?
Sweet like honey
Karma is a cat
Purring in my lap
'cause it loves me
Flexing like
a goddamn acrobat
Me and karma vibe like that
Ask me what I learned
from all those years
Ask me what I earned
from all those tears
Ask me why so many fade
but I'm still here
I'm still. I'm still here
'Cause karma is the thunder
Rattling your ground
Karma's on your scent
like a bounty hunter
Karma's gonna
track you down
Step by step
from town to town
Sweet like justice
Karma is a queen
Karma takes all my friends
to the summit
Karma is the guy
on the screen
Coming straight home to me
'Cause karma is my boyfriend
Karma is a god
Karma is the breeze
in my hair on the weekend
Karma's a relaxing thought
Aren't you envious
that for you it's not?
Sweet like honey
Karma is a cat
Purring in my lap
'cause it loves me
Flexing like
a goddamn acrobat
Me and karma vibe like that
Karma is my boyfriend
- Karma is a god
- BACKUP SINGERS:
Karma's a relaxing thought
LA. cada pessoa neste palco
ama vocês demais.
Por favor. retribuam o amor
para meus incríveis dançarinos!
Por favor. palmas
pra minhas fantásticas backing vocals!
E. por favor. direcionem sua atenção
para o palco principal
e aplausos para minha banda fenomenal!
Amo vocês.
APRESENTAÇÕES EXTRAS
Combat
I'm ready for combat
I say I don't want that
But what if I do?
'Cause cruelty
Wins in the movies
I've got 100
thrown-out speeches
I almost said to you
Easy they come
Easy they go
I jump from the train
I ride off alone
I never grew up
It's getting so old
Help me hold onto you
I've been the archer
I've been the prey
Who could ever
leave me. darling?
But who could stay?
Dark side
I search for your dark side
But what if I'm all right
Right. right. right here?
And I cut off
My nose
just to spite my face
Then I hate my reflection
For years and years
I wake in the night
I pace like a ghost
The room is on fire
Invisible smoke
And all of my heroes
die all alone
Help me hold onto you
I've been the archer
I've been the prey
Screaming. who could
ever leave me. darling...
But who could stay?
'Cause they see
right through me
They see right through me
They see right through
Can you see right through me?
They see right through me
I see right through me
All the king's horses
All the king's men
Couldn't put me
together again
'Cause all of my enemies
started out friends
Help me hold onto you
I've been the archer
I've been the prey
Who could ever
leave me. darling...
But who could stay?
Who could stay?
You could stay
Combat
I'm ready for combat
He said
"Let's get out of this town"
Drive out of this city
away from the crowds
I thought
"Heaven can't help me now"
Nothing lasts forever
But this is gonna
take me down
He's so tall
and handsome as hell
He's so bad
but he does it so well
I can see the end
as it begins
My one condition is...
Say you'll remember me
Standing in a nice dress
Staring at the sunset. babe
Red lips and rosy cheeks
Say you'll see me again
Even if it's just in your
Wildest dreams
ha
You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night
Burning it down
Someday when you leave me
I bet these memories
Follow you around...
You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night
Burning it down
Someday when you leave me
I bet these memories
Follow you around...
You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night
Burning it down
Someday when you leave me
I bet these memories
Follow you around
You'll see me in hindsight
Tangled up with you all night
Burning it down
Someday when you leave me
I bet these memories
Follow you around
I said
Remember this moment
In the back of my mind
The time we stood
with our shaking hands
The crowds in stands went wild
We were
the kings and the queens
And they read off our names
The night you danced like
you knew our lives
Would never be the same
You held your head
like a hero
On a history book page
It was the end of a decade
But the start of an age
Long live
the walls we crashed through
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
I was screaming Long
live all the magic we made
And bring on
all the pretenders
One day
we will be remembered
I said
Remember this feeling
I pass the pictures around
Of all the years
that we stood there
On the sidelines
wishing for right now
We are
the kings and the queens
You traded your baseball cap
for a crown
When they gave us
our trophies
And we held them up
for our town
And the cynics were outraged
Screaming. this is absurd
'Cause for a moment a band
of thieves in ripped-up jeans
Got to rule the world
Long live the walls
we crashed through
How the kingdom lights
shined just for me and you
I was screaming Long
live all the magic we made
And bring on all the
pretenders I'm not afraid
Long live all the
mountains we moved
I had the time of my life
fighting dragons with you
I was screaming Long
live that look on your face
And bring on
all the pretenders
One day
we will be remembered
Hold on
to spinning around
Confetti falls
to the ground
May these memories
break our fall
Will you take a moment
Promise me this
That you'll
stand by me forever
But if. God forbid
Fate should step in
And force us into a goodbye-
If you have children someday
When they point
to the pictures
Please tell them my name
Tell them how
the crowds went wild
I hope they shine
Long live
the walls we crashed through
I had the time of my life
With you
Long. long live
the walls we crashed through
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
And I was screaming Long
live all the magic we made
And bring on all the
pretenders I'm not afraid
Singing long live
all the mountains we moved
I had the time of my life
fighting dragons with you
And long. long live
the look on your face
And bring on
all the pretenders
One day
We will be remembered
I said
Remember this moment
In the back of my mind
The time we stood
with our shaking hands
The crowds in stands went wild
We were
the kings and the queens
And they read off our names
The night you danced like
you knew our lives
Would never be the same
You held your head
like a hero
On a history book page
It was the end of a decade
But the start of an age
Long live
the walls we crashed through
UM MUITO OBRIGADA
À GRANDE EQUIPE DA 13 MANAGEMENT
E À BRILHANTE EQUIPE DA TURNÊ
NOS BASTIDORES
QUE FIZERAM ESTA TURNÊ SER POSSÍVEL.
And bring on
all the pretenders
One day
we will be remembered
I said
Remember this feeling
I'll pass the pictures around
Of all the years
that we stood there
On the sidelines
wishing for right now
We are
the kings and the queens
You traded your baseball cap
for a crown
When they gave us
our trophies
And we held them up
for our town
And the cynics were outraged
Screaming. this is absurd
'Cause for a moment a band
of thieves in ripped-up jeans
Got to rule the world
Long live the walls
we crashed through
How the kingdom lights
shined just for me and you
I was screaming Long
live all the magic we made
And bring on all the
pretenders I'm not afraid
Long live all the
mountains we moved
I had the time of my life
fighting dragons with you
I was screaming Long
live that look on your face
And bring on
all the pretenders
One day
we will be remembered
Hold on
to spinning around
Confetti falls to the ground
May these memories
break our fall
Will you take a moment
Promise me this
That you'll
stand by me forever
But if. God forbid
Fate should step in
And force us into a goodbye
If you have children someday
When they point
to the pictures
Please tell them my name
Tell them how
the crowds went wild
I hope they shine
Long live
the walls we crashed through
I had the time of my life
With you
Long. long live
the walls we crashed through
How the kingdom lights shined
just for me and you
And I was screaming Long
live all the magic we made
And bring on all the
pretenders I'm not afraid
Singing long live
all the mountains we moved
I had the time of my life
fighting dragons with you
And long. long live
the look on your face
OBRIGADA AOS FÃS MAIS GENEROSOS
E ATENCIOSOS DO PLANETA
TUDO ISSO É GRAÇAS A VOCÊS
Sincronização lyrics  >>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org